{
    "subject": "Noboru_Iguchi",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "RoboGeisha",
    "human_readable": "Noboru Iguchi created RoboGeisha.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8374685645103455,
            "question": "Who created RoboGeisha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6195680499076843,
            "question": "Is there a specific purpose behind the creation of RoboGeisha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6121112704277039,
            "question": "What is the name of the creation by Noboru Iguchi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5497698187828064,
            "question": "Are there any other creations by Noboru Iguchi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43549999594688416,
            "question": "What field or industry is Noboru Iguchi involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4062897562980652,
            "question": "What type of entity is RoboGeisha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40349671244621277,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about RoboGeisha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3744182884693146,
            "question": "What are the characteristics of RoboGeisha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34355345368385315,
            "question": "How does RoboGeisha function?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32274317741394043,
            "question": "Where can I learn more about RoboGeisha?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Noboru Iguchi created RoboGeisha.",
            "html": "yago_17987_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does RoboGeisha function?",
            "html": "yago_17987_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the characteristics of RoboGeisha?",
            "html": "yago_17987_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about RoboGeisha?",
            "html": "yago_17987_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17987_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17987_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17987_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17987_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17987_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17987_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17987_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17987_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17987_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17987_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The document file_path=/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17987/re-ranker-msmarco/68.txt contains information about the plot of RoboGeisha, which mentions that Yoshie (Aya Kiguchi) is a robogeisha and destroys the villainous robot.\n* The document file_path=/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17987/re-ranker-msmarco/52.txt contains information about Robo Geisha, which mentions that Noboru Iguchi directed the film.\n\nBased on this analysis, I conclude that:\n\n* The triple \"Noboru Iguchi created RoboGeisha\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly mention that Noboru Iguchi directed and created the film \"RoboGeisha.\" Therefore, the statement \"Noboru Iguchi created RoboGeisha\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}